hello I'm Basel rasor and I've been
asked by the credential Insurance
Company of America to tell you about
their Splendid sickness and accident
programs we all know how suddenly a
sickness and accident can strike
[Music]
how seldom there's any warning and how
important it is to have checks coming in
regularly to pay the bills sickness and
accident can be even more disastrous
when it strikes at the person who brings
home the paycheck because as long as
he's unable to work because of
[Applause]
[Music]
sickness that's how long the family may
have to do without the money so
necessary to pay the everyday expenses
of living the credential offers you
sickness and accident programs that can
help take the place of that missing
paycheck that means money for food
clothing for the many Necessities that
must be ATT
there are also credential plans that can
help pay for those hospital and surgical
expenses that often Mount up to a
sizable sum basically then these plans
are designed to help protect your family
against financial disaster that so often
accompanies physical disaster to one of
its
members in my work I'm constantly
exposed to risks but I protect myself
completely with my credential sickness
and accident
plans because you can't predict what
even the next moment has in store for
you see your credential agent